<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>art on starbeam.one Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/categories/art/</link>
    <description>Recent content in art on starbeam.one Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 06:27:01 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.starbeam.one/categories/art/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>June 2023 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/06/june-2023-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 06:27:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/06/june-2023-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Alpha IV Yay, we made it. Welcome to Alpha IV, which is the fourth alpha release of starbeam.one. We&amp;rsquo;re releasing a new alpha every two months on our push to beta which should occur in October. 🤞
This was a better alpha for me, with Alpha III being a bit of a stressful push. Alpha IV was better and I felt like I was able to get more done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 2023 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/03/march-2023-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 04:14:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/03/march-2023-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Yay, the first Tuesday of every month, time for a monthly status update! Erm, wait, it&amp;rsquo;s Wednesday, huh. With all the hustle and bustle of running starbeam.one lately, I&amp;rsquo;ve dedicated Tuesday to creating and publishing the Stand-up &amp;amp; Shine (&amp;amp; Shill) video, and then Wednesday to announcing it here with this blog. ✌
1,500 Flares of Volume (500 in 2 weeks 🤯) It seems like only two weeks ago we managed to reach our first 1,000 Flares of volume after 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Alpha II</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/02/announcing-alpha-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 06:13:37 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/02/announcing-alpha-ii/</guid>
      <description>Today, I am announcing starbeam.one&amp;rsquo;s Alpha II. This is the second released alpha for our emerging platform and has a focus on our markets and quality. This particular alpha has been quite some time in the making, taking over four months since our Alpha I announcement.
One-Year Anniversary One year ago today, after spending over two years in development solitude and surviving a pandemic, I announced the Alpha Preview to much fan fare and overwhelming market acclaim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2023 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/02/february-2023-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 04:33:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/02/february-2023-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Hello February! It is the first Tuesday (or Wednesday as of late 😇) of the month and therefore time for your starbeam.one monthly status update.
Nearly One Year Has Passed 🚀 I announced the preview on February 22, 2022. Can you believe that in two weeks that will be one full year? 🤯 This time last year I was uploading the different applications to Azure and learning a lot. One year later, we are actively generating revenue and running a business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2023 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/01/january-2023-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 04:27:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/01/january-2023-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Hello out there and welcome to the latest starbeam.one monthly update. As you know, I usually aim to have these out on the first Tuesday of every month. While I was able to attend to the video recording for Stand-up &amp;amp; Shine yesterday, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to get to everything else, so here we are. 🥳
Happy New Year! With that, I would like to wish everyone a happy 2023. May it be a successful one for you and all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/12/december-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 04:07:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/12/december-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Season&amp;rsquo;s greetings!
Woohoo, the first week of the month, and that means a status update for starbeam.one! ✨🚀
500 Sales! Nearly 150 Flares ($150) in Volume! We continue our completely organic non-advertising push here to build our market. As expected, this is a slow process but one that helps build confidence in the system at a slow and steady pace.
As this is my first rodeo into the modern market I am OK with taking my time before bringing on new users through financial spending.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/09/september-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 14:43:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/09/september-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the first Tuesday of every month, meaning your latest starbeam.one status update is here. Let&amp;rsquo;s begin!
Finishing Tasks The past few weeks have been really focused on the Administration Application, which can be viewed as a CMS application around the entire starbeam.one system. I wanted a way to quickly jump through all the different entities of the system and I am pleased to say that I finally have a first version that I am happy with using.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/06/june-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 15:21:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/06/june-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Introducing the Friends &amp;amp; Family Alpha Today, I am pleased to announce the Friends &amp;amp; Family Alpha available for use at alpha.starbeam.one.
What is It? The friends and family alpha is pretty much the same product and release as the alpha preview released back in February but with the addition of commerce providers, which allows real &amp;ldquo;live&amp;rdquo; money for use within the system. We now feature the following commerce providers for purchasing Flares, starbeam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/05/may-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 14:19:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/05/may-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Welcome! Hello out there and welcome to your monthly starbeam.one update, which occurs on the first Tuesday of every month.
Things Are Better Now Last month featured all sorts of problems, which I am glad to say most if not all have been resolved. Rather than a raging inferno, the landscape is more of a (manageable 😁) smoldering mess. I have attended to most of the pressing concerns and have moved onto building features again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/04/april-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 05:18:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/04/april-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Why hello there! It&amp;rsquo;s the first Tuesday of the month, which means it&amp;rsquo;s time for your next installment of starbeam.one monthly status updates.
Everything is on Fire&amp;hellip; Sometimes the expression &amp;ldquo;on fire&amp;rdquo; can be a good thing. Most of the times it is not. Currently, the state of this project is in the latter, unfortunately. Every day seems like a new challenge or something else breaking. I am currently attending to each one as the only person on this project at the moment and making due with the resources and limitations presented to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing MVP Alpha Preview</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/02/announcing-mvp-alpha-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 06:37:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/02/announcing-mvp-alpha-preview/</guid>
      <description>What Now?! WOW&amp;hellip; today is the day, and I am beside myself to finally be here and make this announcement. Today marks the result of over two years of development on a single goal, having started in October 2019: to create a centralized marketplace where users can sell and resell digital ownership in the form of digital licenses.
What the Heck is this thing?! starbeam.one is a Digital Publishing Starship™ that allows you to purchase and resell digital licenses produced by artists on a provided primary and secondary markets, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/may-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 02:24:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/may-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Goodness, what a run. I have basically been on a development tear since the last check-in, clocking about 10-12 hours a day. I guess that&amp;rsquo;s my typical schedule, but all of it has been totally dedicated to disciplined development, which is the ideal.
So upon last check-in I believe I was spilling about having some videos done by now, which WAS ALL A LIE. 😅 Shows you for taking the time to believe me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/02/february-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 03:35:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/02/february-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Well, another checkin so it must mean I am stuck somewhere again. 😁 Indeed, another bout of &amp;ldquo;The Analysis&amp;rdquo; has struck, so I am left staring at the ceiling for hours at a time, awaiting the inspiration to save me.
There&amp;rsquo;s also Twitter, which I find myself switching to uncontrollably to find the latest news &amp;ndash; whatever it may be.
I am getting close, however. This is the last task involving &amp;ldquo;new&amp;rdquo; analysis, and this is one of three tasks (or stories) remaining.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/01/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 01:59:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/01/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello world!
I am excited to announce my efforts here with The Starbeam Project. Although, in my life I have found that it is best not to mention intention and plans but to actually put forth the effort.
If all goes well, this project will represent the next phase and major chapter in my life. I am pretty pumped about this vision and plan to spend the next several years developing it in one form or another.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
