<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>status on starbeam.one Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/tags/status/</link>
    <description>Recent content in status on starbeam.one Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 05:35:23 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.starbeam.one/tags/status/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>January 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/01/january-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 05:35:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/01/january-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Well well&amp;hellip; Happy New Year out there and hope everyone is doing well as they read this, considering the current circumstances and environment we find ourselves in this otherwise promising new year.
Let&amp;rsquo;s get on with the latest update here.
Playground Alpha Feature Complete To start, I am pleased to announce that the playground alpha is feature complete and ready for deployment.
What that means is that the Playground Alpha, slated for availability next month, will allow you to use all the features of starbeam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/12/december-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 06:13:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/12/december-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Greetings and Happy Holidays. Here is your next installment of starbeam.one monthly updates.
I feel the need to say this each time, but yes, I am still alive. 😊 I am also a bit late this time around, having skipped the November update. Originally, I was aiming for the middle of November, but the final feature task that I was working on took way longer than I anticipated&amp;hellip; again. 😅😭</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/10/october-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 03:50:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/10/october-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Goodness, has it been two months already? I have been in a total coding slog since the last checkin, having to battle two coding fronts that address technical debt concerns:
 Identity System (95% complete) Entity Framework Data Access Refactor (65% complete)  The Entity Framework story is a bit further along than it suggests. Part of the issue is that currently all worker processes run in session scope, which makes sense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/08/august-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 07:30:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/08/august-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Well I am still kicking and coding here. I wanted to take a breath here and check in with progress. Not that there is much of any. 😅😭
While I have been plugging some insane hours lately, I have recently been ambushed by the identity system. It was basically like writing a whole new application. What I have built, however, is pretty neat and I am happy with it. Unfortunately, it has pushed my schedule out further, however, so I am trying to deal with the anxiety that goes along with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/07/july-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 09:53:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/07/july-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Well it&amp;rsquo;s July, and as mentioned last time, it&amp;rsquo;s time to take a break. Except&amp;hellip; I don&amp;rsquo;t want to take a break. 😅😭 I think I mentioned that I am working on the identity system. Indeed, I have taken a wrecking ball to this sucker and it is now officially wrecked. I&amp;rsquo;ve been picking up the pieces and putting them back together, but it&amp;rsquo;s been taking WAY longer than expected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/06/june-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 03:56:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/06/june-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Well, alright. After all the commotion of last month, I&amp;rsquo;ve been finding it quite difficult to settle down and get back into the development groove.
What I find interesting is that my life is quite perfect right now for development (ala no emails, etc.), and even then it takes several days if not a full week to get me back in the zone for the 10-12 hour day slog.
Naturally, such a long time-to-focus process gives me a lot of concern for when things get &amp;ldquo;busy&amp;rdquo; (ala the email train) again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/may-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 02:24:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/may-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Goodness, what a run. I have basically been on a development tear since the last check-in, clocking about 10-12 hours a day. I guess that&amp;rsquo;s my typical schedule, but all of it has been totally dedicated to disciplined development, which is the ideal.
So upon last check-in I believe I was spilling about having some videos done by now, which WAS ALL A LIE. 😅 Shows you for taking the time to believe me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/03/march-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 03:00:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/03/march-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Aw jyea&amp;hellip; I am finding myself with the time to write a status update, so that must mean I am in another creative jam. 😆
Well it&amp;rsquo;s not that bad, but I thought I would take a few seconds to chime in here. Things are going pretty well. I am down to one last feature item, which should take about two weeks (🤞). Then after that, it&amp;rsquo;s off to the races with completing deferred tasks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/01/january-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/01/january-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Happy New Year&amp;hellip; ish. 😁 I am having a little down time &amp;ndash; a case of the January&amp;rsquo;s as it were &amp;ndash; so I decided to check in here with a little update.
Things are actually running at a pretty good clip here. In fact, I hesitate to mention it but I am in a bit of a groove as of late, pretty much writing solutions and supporting code at will.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
