<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>status on starbeam.one Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/tags/status/</link>
    <description>Recent content in status on starbeam.one Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 04:07:30 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.starbeam.one/tags/status/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>December 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/12/december-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 04:07:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/12/december-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Season&amp;rsquo;s greetings!
Woohoo, the first week of the month, and that means a status update for starbeam.one! ✨🚀
500 Sales! Nearly 150 Flares ($150) in Volume! We continue our completely organic non-advertising push here to build our market. As expected, this is a slow process but one that helps build confidence in the system at a slow and steady pace. As this is my first rodeo into the modern market I am OK with taking my time before bringing on new users through financial spending.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/11/november-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 06:05:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/11/november-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the second Tuesday of the month, which means we&amp;rsquo;re way overdue for a monthly status update!
A Week Off It is indeed the second Tuesday of the month. I usually aim for the first Tuesday, but I have recently been running into troubles with my recording software and they have been thankfully resolved. So today we are back on track, recording today and again in two weeks from now on the 22nd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/10/october-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 07:54:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/10/october-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Woohoo it&amp;rsquo;s the first Tuesday of the month. That means it&amp;rsquo;s time for your latest monthly starbeam.one status update. ✨
Welcome to the Phase I Alpha! Today marks the official beginning of the Phase I Alpha (or &amp;ldquo;Alpha I&amp;rdquo;) of starbeam.one. As you might recall, we started with the preview back in February, and then the Friends &amp;amp; Family Alpha in June.
Since then it&amp;rsquo;s been a mad dash to arrive to this point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/09/september-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 14:43:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/09/september-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the first Tuesday of every month, meaning your latest starbeam.one status update is here. Let&amp;rsquo;s begin!
Finishing Tasks The past few weeks have been really focused on the Administration Application, which can be viewed as a CMS application around the entire starbeam.one system. I wanted a way to quickly jump through all the different entities of the system and I am pleased to say that I finally have a first version that I am happy with using.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/08/august-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 07:42:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/08/august-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Welcome! It&amp;rsquo;s the first Tuesday of every month, and that means the latest starbeam.one Status Update! Let&amp;rsquo;s begin here.
Program Notes Astute readers will realize that I am posting this on a Thursday, and not a Tuesday. While I was able to record the latest Stand-up &amp;amp; Shine (and Shill) on Tuesday, I was not able to post it until this morning. There were a few issues with post-video production that took quite a bit of time and retakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/07/july-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 06:28:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/07/july-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the first Tuesday of the month, and you know what that means!
It&amp;rsquo;s time for your starbeam.one monthly update.
It Be Awkward There&amp;rsquo;s an expression that I learned from Jim Caldwell, a former Detroit Lions coach (and still my favorite after Jim Schwartz). He used an expression that, turns out, is also used in the military: get comfortable being uncomfortable.
That&amp;rsquo;s sort of where I am at with the present moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/06/june-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 15:21:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/06/june-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Introducing the Friends &amp;amp; Family Alpha Today, I am pleased to announce the Friends &amp;amp; Family Alpha available for use at alpha.starbeam.one.
What is It? The friends and family alpha is pretty much the same product and release as the alpha preview released back in February but with the addition of commerce providers, which allows real &amp;ldquo;live&amp;rdquo; money for use within the system. We now feature the following commerce providers for purchasing Flares, starbeam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/05/may-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 14:19:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/05/may-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Welcome! Hello out there and welcome to your monthly starbeam.one update, which occurs on the first Tuesday of every month.
Things Are Better Now Last month featured all sorts of problems, which I am glad to say most if not all have been resolved. Rather than a raging inferno, the landscape is more of a (manageable 😁) smoldering mess. I have attended to most of the pressing concerns and have moved onto building features again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/04/april-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 05:18:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/04/april-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Why hello there! It&amp;rsquo;s the first Tuesday of the month, which means it&amp;rsquo;s time for your next installment of starbeam.one monthly status updates.
Everything is on Fire&amp;hellip; Sometimes the expression &amp;ldquo;on fire&amp;rdquo; can be a good thing. Most of the times it is not. Currently, the state of this project is in the latter, unfortunately. Every day seems like a new challenge or something else breaking. I am currently attending to each one as the only person on this project at the moment and making due with the resources and limitations presented to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/01/february-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 13:40:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/01/february-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the next installment of monthly starbeam.one updates.
Playground Alpha Deployed to Azure In the last status update, I mentioned that my focus for January was getting the Playground Alpha deployed to Azure. I am pleased to announce that this was accomplished after much configuration and trial+error (and much more error!).
The Playground Alpha is deployed to Azure, and I have been totally blown away by how relatively easy it was to do so, despite all the challenges and errors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/01/january-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 05:35:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/01/january-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Well well&amp;hellip; Happy New Year out there and hope everyone is doing well as they read this, considering the current circumstances and environment we find ourselves in this otherwise promising new year.
Let&amp;rsquo;s get on with the latest update here&amp;hellip;
Playground Alpha Feature Complete To start, I am pleased to announce that the playground alpha is feature complete and ready for deployment.
What that means is that the Playground Alpha, slated for availability next month, will allow you to use all the features of starbeam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/12/december-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 06:13:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/12/december-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Greetings and Happy Holidays. Here is your next installment of starbeam.one monthly updates.
I feel the need to say this each time, but yes, I am still alive. 😊 I am also a bit late this time around, having skipped the November update. Originally, I was aiming for the middle of November, but the final feature task that I was working on took way longer than I anticipated&amp;hellip; again. 😅😭</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/10/october-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 03:50:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/10/october-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Goodness, has it been two months already? I have been in a total coding slog since the last checkin, having to battle two coding fronts that address technical debt concerns:
 Identity System (95% complete) Entity Framework Data Access Refactor (65% complete)  The Entity Framework story is a bit further along than it suggests. Part of the issue is that currently all worker processes run in session scope, which makes sense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/08/august-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 07:30:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/08/august-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Well I am still kicking and coding here. I wanted to take a breath here and check in with progress. Not that there is much of any. 😅😭
While I have been plugging some insane hours lately, I have recently been ambushed by the identity system. It was basically like writing a whole new application. What I have built, however, is pretty neat and I am happy with it. Unfortunately, it has pushed my schedule out further, however, so I am trying to deal with the anxiety that goes along with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/07/july-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 09:53:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/07/july-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Well it&amp;rsquo;s July, and as mentioned last time, it&amp;rsquo;s time to take a break. Except&amp;hellip; I don&amp;rsquo;t want to take a break. 😅😭 I think I mentioned that I am working on the identity system. Indeed, I have taken a wrecking ball to this sucker and it is now officially wrecked. I&amp;rsquo;ve been picking up the pieces and putting them back together, but it&amp;rsquo;s been taking WAY longer than expected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/06/june-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 03:56:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/06/june-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Well, alright. After all the commotion of last month, I&amp;rsquo;ve been finding it quite difficult to settle down and get back into the development groove.
What I find interesting is that my life is quite perfect right now for development (ala no emails, etc.), and even then it takes several days if not a full week to get me back in the zone for the 10-12 hour day slog.
Naturally, such a long time-to-focus process gives me a lot of concern for when things get &amp;ldquo;busy&amp;rdquo; (ala the email train) again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/may-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 02:24:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/may-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Goodness, what a run. I have basically been on a development tear since the last check-in, clocking about 10-12 hours a day. I guess that&amp;rsquo;s my typical schedule, but all of it has been totally dedicated to disciplined development, which is the ideal.
So upon last check-in I believe I was spilling about having some videos done by now, which WAS ALL A LIE. 😅 Shows you for taking the time to believe me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/03/march-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 03:00:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/03/march-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Aw jyea&amp;hellip; I am finding myself with the time to write a status update, so that must mean I am in another creative jam. 😆
Well it&amp;rsquo;s not that bad, but I thought I would take a few seconds to chime in here. Things are going pretty well. I am down to one last feature item, which should take about two weeks (🤞). Then after that, it&amp;rsquo;s off to the races with completing deferred tasks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/01/january-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/01/january-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Happy New Year&amp;hellip; ish. 😁 I am having a little down time &amp;ndash; a case of the January&amp;rsquo;s as it were &amp;ndash; so I decided to check in here with a little update.
Things are actually running at a pretty good clip here. In fact, I hesitate to mention it but I am in a bit of a groove as of late, pretty much writing solutions and supporting code at will.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
