<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>technology on starbeam.one Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/categories/technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in technology on starbeam.one Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:22:01 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.starbeam.one/categories/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Blockchain is Just an Application</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/the-blockchain-is-just-an-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:22:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/the-blockchain-is-just-an-application/</guid>
      <description>The blockchain is just an application. Everyone is going nuts over blockchain now that they see it can be used for commerce, despite its awkwardness and efficiency concerns. In the hysteria, the whole premise of the blockchain has taken on a bigger concept than it actually is.
But let&amp;rsquo;s keep in mind that a blockchain is basically an application. It&amp;rsquo;s an application that runs on one or more computers (nodes) that comprise a network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Opportunity as I See It</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/the-opportunity-as-i-see-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 09:14:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/the-opportunity-as-i-see-it/</guid>
      <description>To my mind, the &amp;ldquo;Creator Economy&amp;rdquo; (buzzwords, ugh) is much like the &amp;ldquo;Real Estate Economy&amp;rdquo; (😛) and can be divided into two segments:
 Digital leasing Digital ownership  Digital leasing should be familiar to anyone who has owned a computer since forever. It&amp;rsquo;s really the only way we have interfaced with digital &amp;ldquo;assets&amp;rdquo; ever since we have been able to copy them into a directory and subsequently paste them infinitely across as many devices we own and/or illicit networks of which we may (or may not 😇) be a member.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/may-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 02:24:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/may-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Goodness, what a run. I have basically been on a development tear since the last check-in, clocking about 10-12 hours a day. I guess that&amp;rsquo;s my typical schedule, but all of it has been totally dedicated to disciplined development, which is the ideal.
So upon last check-in I believe I was spilling about having some videos done by now, which WAS ALL A LIE. 😅 Shows you for taking the time to believe me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/02/february-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 03:35:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/02/february-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Well, another checkin so it must mean I am stuck somewhere again. 😁 Indeed, another bout of &amp;ldquo;The Analysis&amp;rdquo; has struck, so I am left staring at the ceiling for hours at a time, awaiting the inspiration to save me.
There&amp;rsquo;s also Twitter, which I find myself switching to uncontrollably to find the latest news &amp;ndash; whatever it may be.
I am getting close, however. This is the last task involving &amp;ldquo;new&amp;rdquo; analysis, and this is one of three tasks (or stories) remaining.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analysis Is the Most Difficult</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/analysis-is-the-most-difficult/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 08:42:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/analysis-is-the-most-difficult/</guid>
      <description>Of all the phases of development, analysis is the most difficult. For me, at least. I am currently the business analyst for my startup. Well, technically, I am every freaking role of my startup as I am the only one working on it right now. However, what I mostly do is analysis, user experience, and of course, software development.
Out of each of those, analysis is the most challenging for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/01/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 01:59:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/01/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello world!
I am excited to announce my efforts here with The Starbeam Project. Although, in my life I have found that it is best not to mention intention and plans but to actually put forth the effort.
If all goes well, this project will represent the next phase and major chapter in my life. I am pretty pumped about this vision and plan to spend the next several years developing it in one form or another.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
