<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>business on starbeam.one Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/categories/business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in business on starbeam.one Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:06:19 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.starbeam.one/categories/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PayPal Payout Fee Adjustments</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/12/paypal-payout-fee-adjustments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:06:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/12/paypal-payout-fee-adjustments/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s New? We have supported PayPal Payouts since the market opened in June 2022. At that time, my impression and understanding was that fees for this service were $0.25 for each payout. It turns out this is accurate, but only for US-only payouts. International payouts are 2%.
This misunderstanding was caught pretty quickly when we started to process international payouts, which comprise a majority of our payouts. I noticed that they were not always $0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2023 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/12/december-2023-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 06:01:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/12/december-2023-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Hello to all out there, and I hope this finds your holiday season well. 🦌⛄🎅❄
It&amp;rsquo;s the first Tuesday of the month, it is time for a monthly status update! 🚀
Welcome to Beta III I am very happy to announce that today we have Beta III. This is mostly a quality release, addressing a lot of issues for administration and user account management.
With this monthly update, I am going to take some time here and reflect where we are here after four years of development, with (at present) another year of runway to make something of it in a viable way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 2023 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/09/september-2023-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 04:24:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/09/september-2023-status-update/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the first full week of the month and that means it&amp;rsquo;s time for the latest starbeam.one status update!
Slow Times on the Starship Things have gotten slow here, a little slower than anticipated! This was expected as I spent more time on developing key features for support and administration. However, the one incident we did not account for was having our premiere artist account inadvertently getting suspended by Twitter. Lady Leah is our top artist with over 10,000 followers and was our primary source of marketing and promotion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 2023 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/08/august-2023-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 05:58:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/08/august-2023-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Believe it or not, we are in the first week of the month, which means the latest starbeam.one Status Update! 🚀
Welcome to Beta I At long last, after nearly four years of development, we are now official in beta quality. Truth be told, we probably have been in beta quality for quite some time now. Based on feedback from several members, I have made the switch to get this officially acknowledged recognized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 2023 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/07/july-2023-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 07:33:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/07/july-2023-status-update/</guid>
      <description>It is the first week of the month which means it&amp;rsquo;s time for the starbeam.one monthly update! Usually this occurs on a Tuesday, but since we were celebrating our nation&amp;rsquo;s birthday yesterday it felt a little unpatriotic to do such an activity. So today it is!
1.6K Flares of Volume in June, 54% More than May Last month I felt like tempting fate by announcing how much volume we did for the month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 2023 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/06/june-2023-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 06:27:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/06/june-2023-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Alpha IV Yay, we made it. Welcome to Alpha IV, which is the fourth alpha release of starbeam.one. We&amp;rsquo;re releasing a new alpha every two months on our push to beta which should occur in October. 🤞
This was a better alpha for me, with Alpha III being a bit of a stressful push. Alpha IV was better and I felt like I was able to get more done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2023 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/05/may-2023-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 04:03:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/05/may-2023-status-update/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the first week of the month, time for your monthly status update for starbeam.one!
Welcome to May We are here in May, with Alpha IV scheduled for launch next month. It is very heads-down for me (a good thing) and this post will be short-and-sweet.
880 Flares of Volume, Passing 3,500 Total Last month we did 880 Flares of volume for the month, which is pretty impressive considering we did 81 total for the month of December.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 2023 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/04/april-2023-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 04:08:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/04/april-2023-status-update/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the first Tuesday of the month, it&amp;rsquo;s time for a monthly status update on starbeam.one! ✨🚀
Welcome to Alpha III Today we&amp;rsquo;re announcing Alpha III, which is mostly comprised of quality improvements.
Alpha III was meant to be a focus on quality and also key features on administration before we start marketing our application in earnest with formal advertising spend. However, with all the sheer commotion of onboarding new users, artists, and collectors, I only managed to get quality improvements into the codebase for this alpha.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 2023 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/03/march-2023-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 04:14:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/03/march-2023-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Yay, the first Tuesday of every month, time for a monthly status update! Erm, wait, it&amp;rsquo;s Wednesday, huh. With all the hustle and bustle of running starbeam.one lately, I&amp;rsquo;ve dedicated Tuesday to creating and publishing the Stand-up &amp;amp; Shine (&amp;amp; Shill) video, and then Wednesday to announcing it here with this blog. ✌
1,500 Flares of Volume (500 in 2 weeks 🤯) It seems like only two weeks ago we managed to reach our first 1,000 Flares of volume after 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Alpha II</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/02/announcing-alpha-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 06:13:37 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/02/announcing-alpha-ii/</guid>
      <description>Today, I am announcing starbeam.one&amp;rsquo;s Alpha II. This is the second released alpha for our emerging platform and has a focus on our markets and quality. This particular alpha has been quite some time in the making, taking over four months since our Alpha I announcement.
One-Year Anniversary One year ago today, after spending over two years in development solitude and surviving a pandemic, I announced the Alpha Preview to much fan fare and overwhelming market acclaim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2023 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/02/february-2023-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 04:33:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/02/february-2023-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Hello February! It is the first Tuesday (or Wednesday as of late 😇) of the month and therefore time for your starbeam.one monthly status update.
Nearly One Year Has Passed 🚀 I announced the preview on February 22, 2022. Can you believe that in two weeks that will be one full year? 🤯 This time last year I was uploading the different applications to Azure and learning a lot. One year later, we are actively generating revenue and running a business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2023 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/01/january-2023-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 04:27:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/01/january-2023-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Hello out there and welcome to the latest starbeam.one monthly update. As you know, I usually aim to have these out on the first Tuesday of every month. While I was able to attend to the video recording for Stand-up &amp;amp; Shine yesterday, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to get to everything else, so here we are. 🥳
Happy New Year! With that, I would like to wish everyone a happy 2023. May it be a successful one for you and all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/12/december-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 04:07:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/12/december-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Season&amp;rsquo;s greetings!
Woohoo, the first week of the month, and that means a status update for starbeam.one! ✨🚀
500 Sales! Nearly 150 Flares ($150) in Volume! We continue our completely organic non-advertising push here to build our market. As expected, this is a slow process but one that helps build confidence in the system at a slow and steady pace.
As this is my first rodeo into the modern market I am OK with taking my time before bringing on new users through financial spending.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/11/november-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 06:05:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/11/november-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the second Tuesday of the month, which means we&amp;rsquo;re way overdue for a monthly status update!
A Week Off It is indeed the second Tuesday of the month. I usually aim for the first Tuesday, but I have recently been running into troubles with my recording software and they have been thankfully resolved. So today we are back on track, recording today and again in two weeks from now on the 22nd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/10/october-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 07:54:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/10/october-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Woohoo it&amp;rsquo;s the first Tuesday of the month. That means it&amp;rsquo;s time for your latest monthly starbeam.one status update. ✨
Welcome to the Phase I Alpha! Today marks the official beginning of the Phase I Alpha (or &amp;ldquo;Alpha I&amp;rdquo;) of starbeam.one. As you might recall, we started with the preview back in February, and then the Friends &amp;amp; Family Alpha in June.
Since then it&amp;rsquo;s been a mad dash to arrive to this point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/09/september-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 14:43:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/09/september-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the first Tuesday of every month, meaning your latest starbeam.one status update is here. Let&amp;rsquo;s begin!
Finishing Tasks The past few weeks have been really focused on the Administration Application, which can be viewed as a CMS application around the entire starbeam.one system. I wanted a way to quickly jump through all the different entities of the system and I am pleased to say that I finally have a first version that I am happy with using.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/08/august-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 07:42:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/08/august-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Welcome! It&amp;rsquo;s the first Tuesday of every month, and that means the latest starbeam.one Status Update! Let&amp;rsquo;s begin here.
Program Notes Astute readers will realize that I am posting this on a Thursday, and not a Tuesday. While I was able to record the latest Stand-up &amp;amp; Shine (and Shill) on Tuesday, I was not able to post it until this morning. There were a few issues with post-video production that took quite a bit of time and retakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/07/july-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 06:28:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/07/july-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the first Tuesday of the month, and you know what that means!
It&amp;rsquo;s time for your starbeam.one monthly update.
It Be Awkward There&amp;rsquo;s an expression that I learned from Jim Caldwell, a former Detroit Lions coach (and still my favorite after Jim Schwartz). He used an expression that, turns out, is also used in the military: get comfortable being uncomfortable.
That&amp;rsquo;s sort of where I am at with the present moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/06/june-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 15:21:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/06/june-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Introducing the Friends &amp;amp; Family Alpha Today, I am pleased to announce the Friends &amp;amp; Family Alpha available for use at alpha.starbeam.one.
What is It? The friends and family alpha is pretty much the same product and release as the alpha preview released back in February but with the addition of commerce providers, which allows real &amp;ldquo;live&amp;rdquo; money for use within the system. We now feature the following commerce providers for purchasing Flares, starbeam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/05/may-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 14:19:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/05/may-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Welcome! Hello out there and welcome to your monthly starbeam.one update, which occurs on the first Tuesday of every month.
Things Are Better Now Last month featured all sorts of problems, which I am glad to say most if not all have been resolved. Rather than a raging inferno, the landscape is more of a (manageable 😁) smoldering mess. I have attended to most of the pressing concerns and have moved onto building features again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/04/april-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 05:18:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/04/april-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Why hello there! It&amp;rsquo;s the first Tuesday of the month, which means it&amp;rsquo;s time for your next installment of starbeam.one monthly status updates.
Everything is on Fire&amp;hellip; Sometimes the expression &amp;ldquo;on fire&amp;rdquo; can be a good thing. Most of the times it is not. Currently, the state of this project is in the latter, unfortunately. Every day seems like a new challenge or something else breaking. I am currently attending to each one as the only person on this project at the moment and making due with the resources and limitations presented to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Stand-up and Shine Weekly Stand-ups</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/03/introducing-stand-up-and-shine-weekly-stand-ups/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 15:56:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/03/introducing-stand-up-and-shine-weekly-stand-ups/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone and welcome to your next installment of starbeam.one monthly updates.
Except, it&amp;rsquo;s no longer monthly, but is now weekly. And it&amp;rsquo;s no longer in a blog, but in a video.
Yes, I am switching up things here a bit with the format here at starbeam.one. Going forward, I am going to attempt to update you with a weekly video update in an agile stand-up format, featuring such topics as:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing MVP Alpha Preview</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/02/announcing-mvp-alpha-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 06:37:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/02/announcing-mvp-alpha-preview/</guid>
      <description>What Now?! WOW&amp;hellip; today is the day, and I am beside myself to finally be here and make this announcement. Today marks the result of over two years of development on a single goal, having started in October 2019: to create a centralized marketplace where users can sell and resell digital ownership in the form of digital licenses.
What the Heck is this thing?! starbeam.one is a Digital Publishing Starship™ that allows you to purchase and resell digital licenses produced by artists on a provided primary and secondary markets, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft for Startups Application Accepted</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/02/microsoft-for-startups-application-accepted/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 12:27:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/02/microsoft-for-startups-application-accepted/</guid>
      <description>Accepted! I am so very happy to announce that Microsoft for Startups has accepted my Founders Hub application!
This is beyond exhilarating for me, as this is the first external validation I have received for my product. This process was very different from the previous one that I experienced with BizSpark. Whereas BizSpark seemed to allow anyone into their program, the Founders Hub application seemed more serious and discerning with its candidates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/01/february-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 13:40:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/01/february-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the next installment of monthly starbeam.one updates.
Playground Alpha Deployed to Azure In the last status update, I mentioned that my focus for January was getting the Playground Alpha deployed to Azure. I am pleased to announce that this was accomplished after much configuration and trial+error (and much more error!).
The Playground Alpha is deployed to Azure, and I have been totally blown away by how relatively easy it was to do so, despite all the challenges and errors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/01/january-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 05:35:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/01/january-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Well well&amp;hellip; Happy New Year out there and hope everyone is doing well as they read this, considering the current circumstances and environment we find ourselves in this otherwise promising new year.
Let&amp;rsquo;s get on with the latest update here&amp;hellip;
Playground Alpha Feature Complete To start, I am pleased to announce that the playground alpha is feature complete and ready for deployment.
What that means is that the Playground Alpha, slated for availability next month, will allow you to use all the features of starbeam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/12/december-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 06:13:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/12/december-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Greetings and Happy Holidays. Here is your next installment of starbeam.one monthly updates.
I feel the need to say this each time, but yes, I am still alive. 😊 I am also a bit late this time around, having skipped the November update. Originally, I was aiming for the middle of November, but the final feature task that I was working on took way longer than I anticipated&amp;hellip; again. 😅😭</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The  Digital License Is a Relationship</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/10/the-digital-license-is-a-relationship/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 04:33:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/10/the-digital-license-is-a-relationship/</guid>
      <description>There is something I have been thinking about lately, and I wanted to be sure to capture it here.
With the whole NFT mania (quite literally what it is), we get the feeling it is more about what people want and desire rather than what is actually there. After all, an NFT in one blockchain isn&amp;rsquo;t exactly unique if it also exists in another. Let&amp;rsquo;s also not forget that any blockchain at any time can be forked, leading to an instant doubling (or worse, if other forks occur) to any &amp;ldquo;unique&amp;rdquo; instance contained within it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/07/july-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 09:53:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/07/july-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Well it&amp;rsquo;s July, and as mentioned last time, it&amp;rsquo;s time to take a break. Except&amp;hellip; I don&amp;rsquo;t want to take a break. 😅😭 I think I mentioned that I am working on the identity system. Indeed, I have taken a wrecking ball to this sucker and it is now officially wrecked. I&amp;rsquo;ve been picking up the pieces and putting them back together, but it&amp;rsquo;s been taking WAY longer than expected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Battlefield Retrospective</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/06/startup-battlefield-retrospective/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 00:34:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/06/startup-battlefield-retrospective/</guid>
      <description>Some time has passed since I got myself riled up and did a very brash thing with the Startup Battlefield 2021 Application. I wanted to put some thoughts here around it as I have found writing helps get me out of my design/development funk. Not that I am in a funk right now, but I&amp;rsquo;d like things to be a bit crisper than they are.
So my feelings on the entire ordeal are a bit conflicted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Private Key Can Be Guessed</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/06/your-private-key-can-be-guessed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 07:40:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/06/your-private-key-can-be-guessed/</guid>
      <description>One final thought here and I&amp;rsquo;ll finish. I promise. 😁
In addition to some of the risks I outlined earlier in this article with regards to cryptocurrency, there&amp;rsquo;s one in particular that I feel needs extra mention. Namely, the private key that keeps your value safe is simply a number: a very very very large number.
That conceivably means that if someone guesses that number, they have access to your wallet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decentralization Is a Foreign Land</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/decentralization-is-a-foreign-land/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 03:32:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/decentralization-is-a-foreign-land/</guid>
      <description>Continuing my spontaneous series here. 😁
I have been studying the decentralized space since late June 2017, so nearly four years now. If I was attending college then you could say that I am a graduate in such matters (assuming I acquired all my credits, something I failed to do in real live BUT I DIGRESS).
There&amp;rsquo;s a certain quality or metric that has seemed elusive to decentralization during that time, and that is adoption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Battlefield 2021 Application</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/startup-battlefield-2021-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 10:42:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/startup-battlefield-2021-application/</guid>
      <description>On our last check-in, I mentioned working on some finishing features and then moving onto videos. WELLLLLLLLL as it turns out, during that time a nifty article popped up across my RSS feed that I could not archive:
Deadline extended: Apply to Startup Battlefield at TC Disrupt 2021
Extended?! Not by one but by TWO weeks? I started to look at the dates and schedule, and a butterflies-in-the-belly notion started to take hold: could I possibly conceive submitting an application to the tippy-top of all tech events and jump for the improbable if not impossible?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publishing vs Gallery</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/publishing-vs-gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:22:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/publishing-vs-gallery/</guid>
      <description>Everyone is trying to get rich off of NFTs. To me, this is a natural extension of the blockchain culture, which emphasizes money and a get-rich (quick) mentality. I am not against this (much 😁), but it does warrant some caution.
To be sure, there&amp;rsquo;s no such thing as a quick buck in life. You might get lucky, sure, but can you replicate this luck at scale? Good luck with that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Blockchain is Just an Application</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/the-blockchain-is-just-an-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:22:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/the-blockchain-is-just-an-application/</guid>
      <description>The blockchain is just an application. Everyone is going nuts over blockchain now that they see it can be used for commerce, despite its awkwardness and efficiency concerns. In the hysteria, the whole premise of the blockchain has taken on a bigger concept than it actually is.
But let&amp;rsquo;s keep in mind that a blockchain is basically an application. It&amp;rsquo;s an application that runs on one or more computers (nodes) that comprise a network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Biggest Threat</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/the-biggest-threat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:05:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/the-biggest-threat/</guid>
      <description>I guess now that I have spent the past week preparing for the Startup Battlefield 2021 Application (seriously, it took a lot!), I am more in the writing mood and can start putting together some additional thoughts around what I have been working on and the field I am entering here with starbeam.one.
Recently I have been assessing risks. Of course, the biggest risk with any company is that it could fail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Opportunity as I See It</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/the-opportunity-as-i-see-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 09:14:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/the-opportunity-as-i-see-it/</guid>
      <description>To my mind, the &amp;ldquo;Creator Economy&amp;rdquo; (buzzwords, ugh) is much like the &amp;ldquo;Real Estate Economy&amp;rdquo; (😛) and can be divided into two segments:
 Digital leasing Digital ownership  Digital leasing should be familiar to anyone who has owned a computer since forever. It&amp;rsquo;s really the only way we have interfaced with digital &amp;ldquo;assets&amp;rdquo; ever since we have been able to copy them into a directory and subsequently paste them infinitely across as many devices we own and/or illicit networks of which we may (or may not 😇) be a member.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/may-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 02:24:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/may-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Goodness, what a run. I have basically been on a development tear since the last check-in, clocking about 10-12 hours a day. I guess that&amp;rsquo;s my typical schedule, but all of it has been totally dedicated to disciplined development, which is the ideal.
So upon last check-in I believe I was spilling about having some videos done by now, which WAS ALL A LIE. 😅 Shows you for taking the time to believe me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/03/march-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 03:00:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/03/march-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Aw jyea&amp;hellip; I am finding myself with the time to write a status update, so that must mean I am in another creative jam. 😆
Well it&amp;rsquo;s not that bad, but I thought I would take a few seconds to chime in here. Things are going pretty well. I am down to one last feature item, which should take about two weeks (🤞). Then after that, it&amp;rsquo;s off to the races with completing deferred tasks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confronting Competition</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/02/confronting-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 05:05:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/02/confronting-competition/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a tough week here. What compounds it is that I was really on a roll there, ahead of schedule and cooking with momentum. That all seems like ancient history right now, so I guess I am spending some of my time here &amp;ldquo;getting my house in order.&amp;rdquo;
First, Twitter is such a distraction. A double-edged sword, really. I use it to find out the latest news, but then I find out about all the sites out there that could be considered &amp;ldquo;my competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/02/february-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 03:35:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/02/february-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Well, another checkin so it must mean I am stuck somewhere again. 😁 Indeed, another bout of &amp;ldquo;The Analysis&amp;rdquo; has struck, so I am left staring at the ceiling for hours at a time, awaiting the inspiration to save me.
There&amp;rsquo;s also Twitter, which I find myself switching to uncontrollably to find the latest news &amp;ndash; whatever it may be.
I am getting close, however. This is the last task involving &amp;ldquo;new&amp;rdquo; analysis, and this is one of three tasks (or stories) remaining.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/01/january-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/01/january-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Happy New Year&amp;hellip; ish. 😁 I am having a little down time &amp;ndash; a case of the January&amp;rsquo;s as it were &amp;ndash; so I decided to check in here with a little update.
Things are actually running at a pretty good clip here. In fact, I hesitate to mention it but I am in a bit of a groove as of late, pretty much writing solutions and supporting code at will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2020 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/12/december-2020-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 02:20:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/12/december-2020-status-update/</guid>
      <description>December 2020&amp;hellip; I cannot believe we&amp;rsquo;re in the final month of the year, yet here we are nonetheless.
I am actually a few weeks behind on this post, but good to have gotten to it late than never.
This past month for me was easily the most productive. In fact, I can finally see the light at the end of the tunnel here. I have been slamming out code and putting things together in a way that has been incredibly rewarding and efficient at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minding Distractions</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/minding-distractions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 02:17:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/minding-distractions/</guid>
      <description>Well I guess I am on a roll here. 😁 I&amp;rsquo;ve been spending some time on Twitter lately, and it&amp;rsquo;s made me realize what a gigantic distraction it is. Not just it, but any social media. It&amp;rsquo;s so addictive, and once you&amp;rsquo;re bought in, it&amp;rsquo;s all the more difficult to ween away.
I abruptly (rage quit) Facebook in 2019. March 14th (Pi Day) to be exact. It totally totally sucked the first year or so for me, because I felt I basically abandoned all my online friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analysis Is the Most Difficult</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/analysis-is-the-most-difficult/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 08:42:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/analysis-is-the-most-difficult/</guid>
      <description>Of all the phases of development, analysis is the most difficult. For me, at least. I am currently the business analyst for my startup. Well, technically, I am every freaking role of my startup as I am the only one working on it right now. However, what I mostly do is analysis, user experience, and of course, software development.
Out of each of those, analysis is the most challenging for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/01/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 01:59:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/01/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello world!
I am excited to announce my efforts here with The Starbeam Project. Although, in my life I have found that it is best not to mention intention and plans but to actually put forth the effort.
If all goes well, this project will represent the next phase and major chapter in my life. I am pretty pumped about this vision and plan to spend the next several years developing it in one form or another.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
