<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>business on The Starbeam Project Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/categories/business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in business on The Starbeam Project Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 02:24:23 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.starbeam.one/categories/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>May 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/may-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 02:24:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/may-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Goodness, what a run. I have basically been on a development tear since the last check-in, clocking about 10-12 hours a day. I guess that&amp;rsquo;s my typical schedule, but all of it has been totally dedicated to disciplined development, which is the ideal.
So upon last check-in I believe I was spilling about having some videos done by now, which WAS ALL A LIE. 😅 Shows you for taking the time to believe me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/03/march-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 03:00:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/03/march-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Aw jyea&amp;hellip; I am finding myself with the time to write a status update, so that must mean I am in another creative jam. 😆
Well it&amp;rsquo;s not that bad, but I thought I would take a few seconds to chime in here. Things are going pretty well. I am down to one last feature item, which should take about two weeks (🤞). Then after that, it&amp;rsquo;s off to the races with completing deferred tasks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confronting Competition</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/02/confronting-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 05:05:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/02/confronting-competition/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a tough week here. What compounds it is that I was really on a roll there, ahead of schedule and cooking with momentum. That all seems like ancient history right now, so I guess I am spending some of my time here &amp;ldquo;getting my house in order.&amp;rdquo;
First, Twitter is such a distraction. A double-edged sword, really. I use it to find out the latest news, but then I find out about all the sites out there that could be considered &amp;ldquo;my competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/02/february-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 03:35:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/02/february-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Well, another checkin so it must mean I am stuck somewhere again. 😁 Indeed, another bout of &amp;ldquo;The Analysis&amp;rdquo; has struck, so I am left staring at the ceiling for hours at a time, awaiting the inspiration to save me.
There&amp;rsquo;s also Twitter, which I find myself switching to uncontrollably to find the latest news &amp;ndash; whatever it may be.
I am getting close, however. This is the last task involving &amp;ldquo;new&amp;rdquo; analysis, and this is one of three tasks (or stories) remaining.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/01/january-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/01/january-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Happy New Year&amp;hellip; ish. 😁 I am having a little down time &amp;ndash; a case of the January&amp;rsquo;s as it were &amp;ndash; so I decided to check in here with a little update.
Things are actually running at a pretty good clip here. In fact, I hesitate to mention it but I am in a bit of a groove as of late, pretty much writing solutions and supporting code at will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2020 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/12/december-2020-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 02:20:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/12/december-2020-status-update/</guid>
      <description>December 2020&amp;hellip; I cannot believe we&amp;rsquo;re in the final month of the year, yet here we are nonetheless.
I am actually a few weeks behind on this post, but good to have gotten to it late than never.
This past month for me was easily the most productive. In fact, I can finally see the light at the end of the tunnel here. I have been slamming out code and putting things together in a way that has been incredibly rewarding and efficient at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minding Distractions</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/minding-distractions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 02:17:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/minding-distractions/</guid>
      <description>Well I guess I am on a roll here. 😁 I&amp;rsquo;ve been spending some time on Twitter lately, and it&amp;rsquo;s made me realize what a gigantic distraction it is. Not just it, but any social media. It&amp;rsquo;s so addictive, and once you&amp;rsquo;re bought in, it&amp;rsquo;s all the more difficult to ween away.
I abruptly (rage quit) Facebook in 2019. March 14th (Pi Day) to be exact. It totally totally sucked the first year or so for me, because I felt I basically abandoned all my online friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analysis Is the Most Difficult</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/analysis-is-the-most-difficult/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 08:42:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/analysis-is-the-most-difficult/</guid>
      <description>Of all the phases of development, analysis is the most difficult. For me, at least. I am currently the business analyst for my startup. Well, technically, I am every freaking role of my startup as I am the only one working on it right now. However, what I mostly do is analysis, user experience, and of course, software development.
Out of each of those, analysis is the most challenging for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/01/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 01:59:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/01/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello world!
I am excited to announce my efforts here with The Starbeam Project. Although, in my life I have found that it is best not to mention intention and plans but to actually put forth the effort.
If all goes well, this project will represent the next phase and major chapter in my life. I am pretty pumped about this vision and plan to spend the next several years developing it in one form or another.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
