<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>business on starbeam.one Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/categories/business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in business on starbeam.one Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 05:35:23 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.starbeam.one/categories/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>January 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/01/january-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 05:35:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/01/january-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Well well&amp;hellip; Happy New Year out there and hope everyone is doing well as they read this, considering the current circumstances and environment we find ourselves in this otherwise promising new year.
Let&amp;rsquo;s get on with the latest update here&amp;hellip;
Playground Alpha Feature Complete To start, I am pleased to announce that the playground alpha is feature complete and ready for deployment.
What that means is that the Playground Alpha, slated for availability next month, will allow you to use all the features of starbeam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/12/december-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 06:13:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/12/december-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Greetings and Happy Holidays. Here is your next installment of starbeam.one monthly updates.
I feel the need to say this each time, but yes, I am still alive. 😊 I am also a bit late this time around, having skipped the November update. Originally, I was aiming for the middle of November, but the final feature task that I was working on took way longer than I anticipated&amp;hellip; again. 😅😭</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The  Digital License Is a Relationship</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/10/the-digital-license-is-a-relationship/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 04:33:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/10/the-digital-license-is-a-relationship/</guid>
      <description>There is something I have been thinking about lately, and I wanted to be sure to capture it here.
With the whole NFT mania (quite literally what it is), we get the feeling it is more about what people want and desire rather than what is actually there. After all, an NFT in one blockchain isn&amp;rsquo;t exactly unique if it also exists in another. Let&amp;rsquo;s also not forget that any blockchain at any time can be forked, leading to an instant doubling (or worse, if other forks occur) to any &amp;ldquo;unique&amp;rdquo; instance contained within it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/07/july-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 09:53:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/07/july-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Well it&amp;rsquo;s July, and as mentioned last time, it&amp;rsquo;s time to take a break. Except&amp;hellip; I don&amp;rsquo;t want to take a break. 😅😭 I think I mentioned that I am working on the identity system. Indeed, I have taken a wrecking ball to this sucker and it is now officially wrecked. I&amp;rsquo;ve been picking up the pieces and putting them back together, but it&amp;rsquo;s been taking WAY longer than expected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Battlefield Retrospective</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/06/startup-battlefield-retrospective/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 00:34:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/06/startup-battlefield-retrospective/</guid>
      <description>Some time has passed since I got myself riled up and did a very brash thing with the Startup Battlefield 2021 Application. I wanted to put some thoughts here around it as I have found writing helps get me out of my design/development funk. Not that I am in a funk right now, but I&amp;rsquo;d like things to be a bit crisper than they are.
So my feelings on the entire ordeal are a bit conflicted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Private Key Can Be Guessed</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/06/your-private-key-can-be-guessed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 07:40:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/06/your-private-key-can-be-guessed/</guid>
      <description>One final thought here and I&amp;rsquo;ll finish. I promise. 😁
In addition to some of the risks I outlined earlier in this article with regards to cryptocurrency, there&amp;rsquo;s one in particular that I feel needs extra mention. Namely, the private key that keeps your value safe is simply a number: a very very very large number.
That conceivably means that if someone guesses that number, they have access to your wallet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decentralization Is a Foreign Land</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/decentralization-is-a-foreign-land/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 03:32:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/decentralization-is-a-foreign-land/</guid>
      <description>Continuing my spontaneous series here. 😁
I have been studying the decentralized space since late June 2017, so nearly four years now. If I was attending college then you could say that I am a graduate in such matters (assuming I acquired all my credits, something I failed to do in real live BUT I DIGRESS).
There&amp;rsquo;s a certain quality or metric that has seemed elusive to decentralization during that time, and that is adoption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Battlefield 2021 Application</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/startup-battlefield-2021-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 10:42:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/startup-battlefield-2021-application/</guid>
      <description>On our last check-in, I mentioned working on some finishing features and then moving onto videos. WELLLLLLLLL as it turns out, during that time a nifty article popped up across my RSS feed that I could not archive:
Deadline extended: Apply to Startup Battlefield at TC Disrupt 2021
Extended?! Not by one but by TWO weeks? I started to look at the dates and schedule, and a butterflies-in-the-belly notion started to take hold: could I possibly conceive submitting an application to the tippy-top of all tech events and jump for the improbable if not impossible?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publishing vs Gallery</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/publishing-vs-gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:22:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/publishing-vs-gallery/</guid>
      <description>Everyone is trying to get rich off of NFTs. To me, this is a natural extension of the blockchain culture, which emphasizes money and a get-rich (quick) mentality. I am not against this (much 😁), but it does warrant some caution.
To be sure, there&amp;rsquo;s no such thing as a quick buck in life. You might get lucky, sure, but can you replicate this luck at scale? Good luck with that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Blockchain is Just an Application</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/the-blockchain-is-just-an-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:22:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/the-blockchain-is-just-an-application/</guid>
      <description>The blockchain is just an application. Everyone is going nuts over blockchain now that they see it can be used for commerce, despite its awkwardness and efficiency concerns. In the hysteria, the whole premise of the blockchain has taken on a bigger concept than it actually is.
But let&amp;rsquo;s keep in mind that a blockchain is basically an application. It&amp;rsquo;s an application that runs on one or more computers (nodes) that comprise a network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Biggest Threat</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/the-biggest-threat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:05:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/the-biggest-threat/</guid>
      <description>I guess now that I have spent the past week preparing for the Startup Battlefield 2021 Application (seriously, it took a lot!), I am more in the writing mood and can start putting together some additional thoughts around what I have been working on and the field I am entering here with starbeam.one.
Recently I have been assessing risks. Of course, the biggest risk with any company is that it could fail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Opportunity as I See It</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/the-opportunity-as-i-see-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 09:14:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/the-opportunity-as-i-see-it/</guid>
      <description>To my mind, the &amp;ldquo;Creator Economy&amp;rdquo; (buzzwords, ugh) is much like the &amp;ldquo;Real Estate Economy&amp;rdquo; (😛) and can be divided into two segments:
 Digital leasing Digital ownership  Digital leasing should be familiar to anyone who has owned a computer since forever. It&amp;rsquo;s really the only way we have interfaced with digital &amp;ldquo;assets&amp;rdquo; ever since we have been able to copy them into a directory and subsequently paste them infinitely across as many devices we own and/or illicit networks of which we may (or may not 😇) be a member.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/may-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 02:24:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/may-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Goodness, what a run. I have basically been on a development tear since the last check-in, clocking about 10-12 hours a day. I guess that&amp;rsquo;s my typical schedule, but all of it has been totally dedicated to disciplined development, which is the ideal.
So upon last check-in I believe I was spilling about having some videos done by now, which WAS ALL A LIE. 😅 Shows you for taking the time to believe me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/03/march-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 03:00:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/03/march-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Aw jyea&amp;hellip; I am finding myself with the time to write a status update, so that must mean I am in another creative jam. 😆
Well it&amp;rsquo;s not that bad, but I thought I would take a few seconds to chime in here. Things are going pretty well. I am down to one last feature item, which should take about two weeks (🤞). Then after that, it&amp;rsquo;s off to the races with completing deferred tasks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confronting Competition</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/02/confronting-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 05:05:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/02/confronting-competition/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a tough week here. What compounds it is that I was really on a roll there, ahead of schedule and cooking with momentum. That all seems like ancient history right now, so I guess I am spending some of my time here &amp;ldquo;getting my house in order.&amp;rdquo;
First, Twitter is such a distraction. A double-edged sword, really. I use it to find out the latest news, but then I find out about all the sites out there that could be considered &amp;ldquo;my competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/02/february-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 03:35:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/02/february-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Well, another checkin so it must mean I am stuck somewhere again. 😁 Indeed, another bout of &amp;ldquo;The Analysis&amp;rdquo; has struck, so I am left staring at the ceiling for hours at a time, awaiting the inspiration to save me.
There&amp;rsquo;s also Twitter, which I find myself switching to uncontrollably to find the latest news &amp;ndash; whatever it may be.
I am getting close, however. This is the last task involving &amp;ldquo;new&amp;rdquo; analysis, and this is one of three tasks (or stories) remaining.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/01/january-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/01/january-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Happy New Year&amp;hellip; ish. 😁 I am having a little down time &amp;ndash; a case of the January&amp;rsquo;s as it were &amp;ndash; so I decided to check in here with a little update.
Things are actually running at a pretty good clip here. In fact, I hesitate to mention it but I am in a bit of a groove as of late, pretty much writing solutions and supporting code at will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2020 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/12/december-2020-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 02:20:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/12/december-2020-status-update/</guid>
      <description>December 2020&amp;hellip; I cannot believe we&amp;rsquo;re in the final month of the year, yet here we are nonetheless.
I am actually a few weeks behind on this post, but good to have gotten to it late than never.
This past month for me was easily the most productive. In fact, I can finally see the light at the end of the tunnel here. I have been slamming out code and putting things together in a way that has been incredibly rewarding and efficient at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minding Distractions</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/minding-distractions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 02:17:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/minding-distractions/</guid>
      <description>Well I guess I am on a roll here. 😁 I&amp;rsquo;ve been spending some time on Twitter lately, and it&amp;rsquo;s made me realize what a gigantic distraction it is. Not just it, but any social media. It&amp;rsquo;s so addictive, and once you&amp;rsquo;re bought in, it&amp;rsquo;s all the more difficult to ween away.
I abruptly (rage quit) Facebook in 2019. March 14th (Pi Day) to be exact. It totally totally sucked the first year or so for me, because I felt I basically abandoned all my online friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analysis Is the Most Difficult</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/analysis-is-the-most-difficult/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 08:42:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/analysis-is-the-most-difficult/</guid>
      <description>Of all the phases of development, analysis is the most difficult. For me, at least. I am currently the business analyst for my startup. Well, technically, I am every freaking role of my startup as I am the only one working on it right now. However, what I mostly do is analysis, user experience, and of course, software development.
Out of each of those, analysis is the most challenging for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/01/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 01:59:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/01/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello world!
I am excited to announce my efforts here with The Starbeam Project. Although, in my life I have found that it is best not to mention intention and plans but to actually put forth the effort.
If all goes well, this project will represent the next phase and major chapter in my life. I am pretty pumped about this vision and plan to spend the next several years developing it in one form or another.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
