<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mike-E on The Starbeam Project Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/authors/mike-e/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mike-E on The Starbeam Project Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 08:42:32 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.starbeam.one/authors/mike-e/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Analysis Is the Most Difficult</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/analysis-is-the-most-difficult/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 08:42:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/analysis-is-the-most-difficult/</guid>
      <description>Of all the phases of development, analysis is the most difficult. For me, at least. I am currently the business analyst for my startup. Well, technically, I am every freaking role of my startup as I am the only one working on it right now. However, what I mostly do is analysis, user experience, and of course, software development.
Out of each of those, analysis is the most challenging for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November 2020 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/november-2020-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 05:44:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/november-2020-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Woooooooooo buddy, am I wayyyyyyyy overdue for a status update here.
I&amp;rsquo;ve actually been thinking about typing up an update for a while.
2020 has been super crazy, and I am no exception. I feel like I have lost 3 months worth of progress and velocity due to the pandemic.
But, I have been lucky enough to keep on plucking along here, developing Starbeam One for majority of the year. In fact, the light at the end of the tunnel is starting to emerge, and I am feeling it&amp;rsquo;s about 3 more months until I am &amp;ldquo;structurally complete&amp;rdquo; (with major stories completed) and then &amp;ldquo;feature complete&amp;rdquo; (all stories needed for an MVP) a few months after that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/01/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 01:59:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/01/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello world!
I am excited to announce my efforts here with The Starbeam Project. Although, in my life I have found that it is best not to mention intention and plans but to actually put forth the effort.
If all goes well, this project will represent the next phase and major chapter in my life. I am pretty pumped about this vision and plan to spend the next several years developing it in one form or another.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
