<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>etc on starbeam.one Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/categories/etc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in etc on starbeam.one Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 13:40:16 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.starbeam.one/categories/etc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>February 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/01/february-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 13:40:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/01/february-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the next installment of monthly starbeam.one updates.
Playground Alpha Deployed to Azure In the last status update, I mentioned that my focus for January was getting the Playground Alpha deployed to Azure. I am pleased to announce that this was accomplished after much configuration and trial+error (and much more error!).
The Playground Alpha is deployed to Azure, and I have been totally blown away by how relatively easy it was to do so, despite all the challenges and errors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/01/january-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 05:35:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/01/january-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Well well&amp;hellip; Happy New Year out there and hope everyone is doing well as they read this, considering the current circumstances and environment we find ourselves in this otherwise promising new year.
Let&amp;rsquo;s get on with the latest update here&amp;hellip;
Playground Alpha Feature Complete To start, I am pleased to announce that the playground alpha is feature complete and ready for deployment.
What that means is that the Playground Alpha, slated for availability next month, will allow you to use all the features of starbeam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/10/october-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 03:50:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/10/october-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Goodness, has it been two months already? I have been in a total coding slog since the last checkin, having to battle two coding fronts that address technical debt concerns:
 Identity System (95% complete) Entity Framework Data Access Refactor (65% complete)  The Entity Framework story is a bit further along than it suggests. Part of the issue is that currently all worker processes run in session scope, which makes sense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/08/august-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 07:30:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/08/august-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Well I am still kicking and coding here. I wanted to take a breath here and check in with progress. Not that there is much of any. 😅😭
While I have been plugging some insane hours lately, I have recently been ambushed by the identity system. It was basically like writing a whole new application. What I have built, however, is pretty neat and I am happy with it. Unfortunately, it has pushed my schedule out further, however, so I am trying to deal with the anxiety that goes along with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/07/july-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 09:53:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/07/july-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Well it&amp;rsquo;s July, and as mentioned last time, it&amp;rsquo;s time to take a break. Except&amp;hellip; I don&amp;rsquo;t want to take a break. 😅😭 I think I mentioned that I am working on the identity system. Indeed, I have taken a wrecking ball to this sucker and it is now officially wrecked. I&amp;rsquo;ve been picking up the pieces and putting them back together, but it&amp;rsquo;s been taking WAY longer than expected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Battlefield Retrospective</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/06/startup-battlefield-retrospective/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 00:34:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/06/startup-battlefield-retrospective/</guid>
      <description>Some time has passed since I got myself riled up and did a very brash thing with the Startup Battlefield 2021 Application. I wanted to put some thoughts here around it as I have found writing helps get me out of my design/development funk. Not that I am in a funk right now, but I&amp;rsquo;d like things to be a bit crisper than they are.
So my feelings on the entire ordeal are a bit conflicted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/06/june-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 03:56:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/06/june-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Well, alright. After all the commotion of last month, I&amp;rsquo;ve been finding it quite difficult to settle down and get back into the development groove.
What I find interesting is that my life is quite perfect right now for development (ala no emails, etc.), and even then it takes several days if not a full week to get me back in the zone for the 10-12 hour day slog.
Naturally, such a long time-to-focus process gives me a lot of concern for when things get &amp;ldquo;busy&amp;rdquo; (ala the email train) again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/may-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 02:24:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/may-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Goodness, what a run. I have basically been on a development tear since the last check-in, clocking about 10-12 hours a day. I guess that&amp;rsquo;s my typical schedule, but all of it has been totally dedicated to disciplined development, which is the ideal.
So upon last check-in I believe I was spilling about having some videos done by now, which WAS ALL A LIE. 😅 Shows you for taking the time to believe me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/03/march-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 03:00:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/03/march-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Aw jyea&amp;hellip; I am finding myself with the time to write a status update, so that must mean I am in another creative jam. 😆
Well it&amp;rsquo;s not that bad, but I thought I would take a few seconds to chime in here. Things are going pretty well. I am down to one last feature item, which should take about two weeks (🤞). Then after that, it&amp;rsquo;s off to the races with completing deferred tasks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/02/february-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 03:35:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/02/february-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Well, another checkin so it must mean I am stuck somewhere again. 😁 Indeed, another bout of &amp;ldquo;The Analysis&amp;rdquo; has struck, so I am left staring at the ceiling for hours at a time, awaiting the inspiration to save me.
There&amp;rsquo;s also Twitter, which I find myself switching to uncontrollably to find the latest news &amp;ndash; whatever it may be.
I am getting close, however. This is the last task involving &amp;ldquo;new&amp;rdquo; analysis, and this is one of three tasks (or stories) remaining.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/01/january-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/01/january-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Happy New Year&amp;hellip; ish. 😁 I am having a little down time &amp;ndash; a case of the January&amp;rsquo;s as it were &amp;ndash; so I decided to check in here with a little update.
Things are actually running at a pretty good clip here. In fact, I hesitate to mention it but I am in a bit of a groove as of late, pretty much writing solutions and supporting code at will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2020 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/12/december-2020-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 02:20:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/12/december-2020-status-update/</guid>
      <description>December 2020&amp;hellip; I cannot believe we&amp;rsquo;re in the final month of the year, yet here we are nonetheless.
I am actually a few weeks behind on this post, but good to have gotten to it late than never.
This past month for me was easily the most productive. In fact, I can finally see the light at the end of the tunnel here. I have been slamming out code and putting things together in a way that has been incredibly rewarding and efficient at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minding Distractions</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/minding-distractions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 02:17:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/minding-distractions/</guid>
      <description>Well I guess I am on a roll here. 😁 I&amp;rsquo;ve been spending some time on Twitter lately, and it&amp;rsquo;s made me realize what a gigantic distraction it is. Not just it, but any social media. It&amp;rsquo;s so addictive, and once you&amp;rsquo;re bought in, it&amp;rsquo;s all the more difficult to ween away.
I abruptly (rage quit) Facebook in 2019. March 14th (Pi Day) to be exact. It totally totally sucked the first year or so for me, because I felt I basically abandoned all my online friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November 2020 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/november-2020-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 05:44:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/november-2020-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Woooooooooo buddy, am I wayyyyyyyy overdue for a status update here.
I&amp;rsquo;ve actually been thinking about typing up an update for a while.
2020 has been super crazy, and I am no exception. I feel like I have lost 3 months worth of progress and velocity due to the pandemic.
But, I have been lucky enough to keep on plucking along here, developing Starbeam One for majority of the year. In fact, the light at the end of the tunnel is starting to emerge, and I am feeling it&amp;rsquo;s about 3 more months until I am &amp;ldquo;structurally complete&amp;rdquo; (with major stories completed) and then &amp;ldquo;feature complete&amp;rdquo; (all stories needed for an MVP) a few months after that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/01/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 01:59:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/01/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello world!
I am excited to announce my efforts here with The Starbeam Project. Although, in my life I have found that it is best not to mention intention and plans but to actually put forth the effort.
If all goes well, this project will represent the next phase and major chapter in my life. I am pretty pumped about this vision and plan to spend the next several years developing it in one form or another.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
