<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>life on The Starbeam Project Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/categories/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in life on The Starbeam Project Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 11:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.starbeam.one/categories/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>January 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/01/january-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/01/january-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Happy New Year&amp;hellip; ish. 😁 I am having a little down time &amp;ndash; a case of the January&amp;rsquo;s as it were &amp;ndash; so I decided to check in here with a little update.
Things are actually running at a pretty good clip here. In fact, I hesitate to mention it but I am in a bit of a groove as of late, pretty much writing solutions and supporting code at will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2020 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/12/december-2020-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 02:20:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/12/december-2020-status-update/</guid>
      <description>December 2020&amp;hellip; I cannot believe we&amp;rsquo;re in the final month of the year, yet here we are nonetheless.
I am actually a few weeks behind on this post, but good to have gotten to it late than never.
This past month for me was easily the most productive. In fact, I can finally see the light at the end of the tunnel here. I have been slamming out code and putting things together in a way that has been incredibly rewarding and efficient at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minding Distractions</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/minding-distractions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 02:17:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/minding-distractions/</guid>
      <description>Well I guess I am on a roll here. 😁 I&amp;rsquo;ve been spending some time on Twitter lately, and it&amp;rsquo;s made me realize what a gigantic distraction it is. Not just it, but any social media. It&amp;rsquo;s so addictive, and once you&amp;rsquo;re bought in, it&amp;rsquo;s all the more difficult to ween away.
I abruptly (rage quit) Facebook in 2019. March 14th (Pi Day) to be exact. It totally totally sucked the first year or so for me, because I felt I basically abandoned all my online friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November 2020 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/november-2020-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 05:44:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/november-2020-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Woooooooooo buddy, am I wayyyyyyyy overdue for a status update here.
I&amp;rsquo;ve actually been thinking about typing up an update for a while.
2020 has been super crazy, and I am no exception. I feel like I have lost 3 months worth of progress and velocity due to the pandemic.
But, I have been lucky enough to keep on plucking along here, developing Starbeam One for majority of the year. In fact, the light at the end of the tunnel is starting to emerge, and I am feeling it&amp;rsquo;s about 3 more months until I am &amp;ldquo;structurally complete&amp;rdquo; (with major stories completed) and then &amp;ldquo;feature complete&amp;rdquo; (all stories needed for an MVP) a few months after that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/01/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 01:59:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/01/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello world!
I am excited to announce my efforts here with The Starbeam Project. Although, in my life I have found that it is best not to mention intention and plans but to actually put forth the effort.
If all goes well, this project will represent the next phase and major chapter in my life. I am pretty pumped about this vision and plan to spend the next several years developing it in one form or another.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
