<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>life on starbeam.one Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/categories/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in life on starbeam.one Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 04:17:58 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.starbeam.one/categories/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>April 2024 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2024/04/april-2024-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 04:17:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2024/04/april-2024-status-update/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the first week of the month here at starbeam.one. This means the latest monthly status update. ✨🚀
v1.1 Released I was finally able to deploy v1.1 last month, which includes all sorts of quality updates to v1.0. With that release I finally caught up with all the technical debt I had been enduring and battling for the past few months. I am so glad that is over and I am able to finally get back to feature development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2023 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/12/december-2023-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 06:01:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/12/december-2023-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Hello to all out there, and I hope this finds your holiday season well. 🦌⛄🎅❄
It&amp;rsquo;s the first Tuesday of the month, it is time for a monthly status update! 🚀
Welcome to Beta III I am very happy to announce that today we have Beta III. This is mostly a quality release, addressing a lot of issues for administration and user account management.
With this monthly update, I am going to take some time here and reflect where we are here after four years of development, with (at present) another year of runway to make something of it in a viable way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 2023 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/09/september-2023-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 04:24:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/09/september-2023-status-update/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the first full week of the month and that means it&amp;rsquo;s time for the latest starbeam.one status update!
Slow Times on the Starship Things have gotten slow here, a little slower than anticipated! This was expected as I spent more time on developing key features for support and administration. However, the one incident we did not account for was having our premiere artist account inadvertently getting suspended by Twitter. Lady Leah is our top artist with over 10,000 followers and was our primary source of marketing and promotion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 2023 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/07/july-2023-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 07:33:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2023/07/july-2023-status-update/</guid>
      <description>It is the first week of the month which means it&amp;rsquo;s time for the starbeam.one monthly update! Usually this occurs on a Tuesday, but since we were celebrating our nation&amp;rsquo;s birthday yesterday it felt a little unpatriotic to do such an activity. So today it is!
1.6K Flares of Volume in June, 54% More than May Last month I felt like tempting fate by announcing how much volume we did for the month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/11/november-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 06:05:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/11/november-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the second Tuesday of the month, which means we&amp;rsquo;re way overdue for a monthly status update!
A Week Off It is indeed the second Tuesday of the month. I usually aim for the first Tuesday, but I have recently been running into troubles with my recording software and they have been thankfully resolved. So today we are back on track, recording today and again in two weeks from now on the 22nd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/10/october-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 07:54:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/10/october-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Woohoo it&amp;rsquo;s the first Tuesday of the month. That means it&amp;rsquo;s time for your latest monthly starbeam.one status update. ✨
Welcome to the Phase I Alpha! Today marks the official beginning of the Phase I Alpha (or &amp;ldquo;Alpha I&amp;rdquo;) of starbeam.one. As you might recall, we started with the preview back in February, and then the Friends &amp;amp; Family Alpha in June.
Since then it&amp;rsquo;s been a mad dash to arrive to this point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/09/september-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 14:43:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/09/september-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the first Tuesday of every month, meaning your latest starbeam.one status update is here. Let&amp;rsquo;s begin!
Finishing Tasks The past few weeks have been really focused on the Administration Application, which can be viewed as a CMS application around the entire starbeam.one system. I wanted a way to quickly jump through all the different entities of the system and I am pleased to say that I finally have a first version that I am happy with using.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/08/august-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 07:42:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/08/august-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Welcome! It&amp;rsquo;s the first Tuesday of every month, and that means the latest starbeam.one Status Update! Let&amp;rsquo;s begin here.
Program Notes Astute readers will realize that I am posting this on a Thursday, and not a Tuesday. While I was able to record the latest Stand-up &amp;amp; Shine (and Shill) on Tuesday, I was not able to post it until this morning. There were a few issues with post-video production that took quite a bit of time and retakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/07/july-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 06:28:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/07/july-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the first Tuesday of the month, and you know what that means!
It&amp;rsquo;s time for your starbeam.one monthly update.
It Be Awkward There&amp;rsquo;s an expression that I learned from Jim Caldwell, a former Detroit Lions coach (and still my favorite after Jim Schwartz). He used an expression that, turns out, is also used in the military: get comfortable being uncomfortable.
That&amp;rsquo;s sort of where I am at with the present moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/06/june-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 15:21:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/06/june-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Introducing the Friends &amp;amp; Family Alpha Today, I am pleased to announce the Friends &amp;amp; Family Alpha available for use at alpha.starbeam.one.
What is It? The friends and family alpha is pretty much the same product and release as the alpha preview released back in February but with the addition of commerce providers, which allows real &amp;ldquo;live&amp;rdquo; money for use within the system. We now feature the following commerce providers for purchasing Flares, starbeam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/05/may-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 14:19:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/05/may-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Welcome! Hello out there and welcome to your monthly starbeam.one update, which occurs on the first Tuesday of every month.
Things Are Better Now Last month featured all sorts of problems, which I am glad to say most if not all have been resolved. Rather than a raging inferno, the landscape is more of a (manageable 😁) smoldering mess. I have attended to most of the pressing concerns and have moved onto building features again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/04/april-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 05:18:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/04/april-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Why hello there! It&amp;rsquo;s the first Tuesday of the month, which means it&amp;rsquo;s time for your next installment of starbeam.one monthly status updates.
Everything is on Fire&amp;hellip; Sometimes the expression &amp;ldquo;on fire&amp;rdquo; can be a good thing. Most of the times it is not. Currently, the state of this project is in the latter, unfortunately. Every day seems like a new challenge or something else breaking. I am currently attending to each one as the only person on this project at the moment and making due with the resources and limitations presented to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Stand-up and Shine Weekly Stand-ups</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/03/introducing-stand-up-and-shine-weekly-stand-ups/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 15:56:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/03/introducing-stand-up-and-shine-weekly-stand-ups/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone and welcome to your next installment of starbeam.one monthly updates.
Except, it&amp;rsquo;s no longer monthly, but is now weekly. And it&amp;rsquo;s no longer in a blog, but in a video.
Yes, I am switching up things here a bit with the format here at starbeam.one. Going forward, I am going to attempt to update you with a weekly video update in an agile stand-up format, featuring such topics as:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing MVP Alpha Preview</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/02/announcing-mvp-alpha-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 06:37:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/02/announcing-mvp-alpha-preview/</guid>
      <description>What Now?! WOW&amp;hellip; today is the day, and I am beside myself to finally be here and make this announcement. Today marks the result of over two years of development on a single goal, having started in October 2019: to create a centralized marketplace where users can sell and resell digital ownership in the form of digital licenses.
What the Heck is this thing?! starbeam.one is a Digital Publishing Starship™ that allows you to purchase and resell digital licenses produced by artists on a provided primary and secondary markets, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft for Startups Application Accepted</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/02/microsoft-for-startups-application-accepted/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 12:27:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/02/microsoft-for-startups-application-accepted/</guid>
      <description>Accepted! I am so very happy to announce that Microsoft for Startups has accepted my Founders Hub application!
This is beyond exhilarating for me, as this is the first external validation I have received for my product. This process was very different from the previous one that I experienced with BizSpark. Whereas BizSpark seemed to allow anyone into their program, the Founders Hub application seemed more serious and discerning with its candidates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2022 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/01/february-2022-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 13:40:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2022/01/february-2022-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the next installment of monthly starbeam.one updates.
Playground Alpha Deployed to Azure In the last status update, I mentioned that my focus for January was getting the Playground Alpha deployed to Azure. I am pleased to announce that this was accomplished after much configuration and trial+error (and much more error!).
The Playground Alpha is deployed to Azure, and I have been totally blown away by how relatively easy it was to do so, despite all the challenges and errors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/12/december-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 06:13:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/12/december-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Greetings and Happy Holidays. Here is your next installment of starbeam.one monthly updates.
I feel the need to say this each time, but yes, I am still alive. 😊 I am also a bit late this time around, having skipped the November update. Originally, I was aiming for the middle of November, but the final feature task that I was working on took way longer than I anticipated&amp;hellip; again. 😅😭</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/07/july-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 09:53:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/07/july-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Well it&amp;rsquo;s July, and as mentioned last time, it&amp;rsquo;s time to take a break. Except&amp;hellip; I don&amp;rsquo;t want to take a break. 😅😭 I think I mentioned that I am working on the identity system. Indeed, I have taken a wrecking ball to this sucker and it is now officially wrecked. I&amp;rsquo;ve been picking up the pieces and putting them back together, but it&amp;rsquo;s been taking WAY longer than expected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Battlefield Retrospective</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/06/startup-battlefield-retrospective/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 00:34:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/06/startup-battlefield-retrospective/</guid>
      <description>Some time has passed since I got myself riled up and did a very brash thing with the Startup Battlefield 2021 Application. I wanted to put some thoughts here around it as I have found writing helps get me out of my design/development funk. Not that I am in a funk right now, but I&amp;rsquo;d like things to be a bit crisper than they are.
So my feelings on the entire ordeal are a bit conflicted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Battlefield 2021 Application</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/startup-battlefield-2021-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 10:42:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/startup-battlefield-2021-application/</guid>
      <description>On our last check-in, I mentioned working on some finishing features and then moving onto videos. WELLLLLLLLL as it turns out, during that time a nifty article popped up across my RSS feed that I could not archive:
Deadline extended: Apply to Startup Battlefield at TC Disrupt 2021
Extended?! Not by one but by TWO weeks? I started to look at the dates and schedule, and a butterflies-in-the-belly notion started to take hold: could I possibly conceive submitting an application to the tippy-top of all tech events and jump for the improbable if not impossible?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/may-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 02:24:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/05/may-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Goodness, what a run. I have basically been on a development tear since the last check-in, clocking about 10-12 hours a day. I guess that&amp;rsquo;s my typical schedule, but all of it has been totally dedicated to disciplined development, which is the ideal.
So upon last check-in I believe I was spilling about having some videos done by now, which WAS ALL A LIE. 😅 Shows you for taking the time to believe me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/03/march-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 03:00:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/03/march-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Aw jyea&amp;hellip; I am finding myself with the time to write a status update, so that must mean I am in another creative jam. 😆
Well it&amp;rsquo;s not that bad, but I thought I would take a few seconds to chime in here. Things are going pretty well. I am down to one last feature item, which should take about two weeks (🤞). Then after that, it&amp;rsquo;s off to the races with completing deferred tasks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confronting Competition</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/02/confronting-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 05:05:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/02/confronting-competition/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a tough week here. What compounds it is that I was really on a roll there, ahead of schedule and cooking with momentum. That all seems like ancient history right now, so I guess I am spending some of my time here &amp;ldquo;getting my house in order.&amp;rdquo;
First, Twitter is such a distraction. A double-edged sword, really. I use it to find out the latest news, but then I find out about all the sites out there that could be considered &amp;ldquo;my competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/02/february-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 03:35:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/02/february-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Well, another checkin so it must mean I am stuck somewhere again. 😁 Indeed, another bout of &amp;ldquo;The Analysis&amp;rdquo; has struck, so I am left staring at the ceiling for hours at a time, awaiting the inspiration to save me.
There&amp;rsquo;s also Twitter, which I find myself switching to uncontrollably to find the latest news &amp;ndash; whatever it may be.
I am getting close, however. This is the last task involving &amp;ldquo;new&amp;rdquo; analysis, and this is one of three tasks (or stories) remaining.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2021 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/01/january-2021-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2021/01/january-2021-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Happy New Year&amp;hellip; ish. 😁 I am having a little down time &amp;ndash; a case of the January&amp;rsquo;s as it were &amp;ndash; so I decided to check in here with a little update.
Things are actually running at a pretty good clip here. In fact, I hesitate to mention it but I am in a bit of a groove as of late, pretty much writing solutions and supporting code at will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2020 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/12/december-2020-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 02:20:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/12/december-2020-status-update/</guid>
      <description>December 2020&amp;hellip; I cannot believe we&amp;rsquo;re in the final month of the year, yet here we are nonetheless.
I am actually a few weeks behind on this post, but good to have gotten to it late than never.
This past month for me was easily the most productive. In fact, I can finally see the light at the end of the tunnel here. I have been slamming out code and putting things together in a way that has been incredibly rewarding and efficient at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minding Distractions</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/minding-distractions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 02:17:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/minding-distractions/</guid>
      <description>Well I guess I am on a roll here. 😁 I&amp;rsquo;ve been spending some time on Twitter lately, and it&amp;rsquo;s made me realize what a gigantic distraction it is. Not just it, but any social media. It&amp;rsquo;s so addictive, and once you&amp;rsquo;re bought in, it&amp;rsquo;s all the more difficult to ween away.
I abruptly (rage quit) Facebook in 2019. March 14th (Pi Day) to be exact. It totally totally sucked the first year or so for me, because I felt I basically abandoned all my online friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November 2020 Status Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/november-2020-status-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 05:44:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/11/november-2020-status-update/</guid>
      <description>Woooooooooo buddy, am I wayyyyyyyy overdue for a status update here.
I&amp;rsquo;ve actually been thinking about typing up an update for a while.
2020 has been super crazy, and I am no exception. I feel like I have lost 3 months worth of progress and velocity due to the pandemic.
But, I have been lucky enough to keep on plucking along here, developing Starbeam One for majority of the year. In fact, the light at the end of the tunnel is starting to emerge, and I am feeling it&amp;rsquo;s about 3 more months until I am &amp;ldquo;structurally complete&amp;rdquo; (with major stories completed) and then &amp;ldquo;feature complete&amp;rdquo; (all stories needed for an MVP) a few months after that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/01/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 01:59:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.starbeam.one/2020/01/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello world!
I am excited to announce my efforts here with The Starbeam Project. Although, in my life I have found that it is best not to mention intention and plans but to actually put forth the effort.
If all goes well, this project will represent the next phase and major chapter in my life. I am pretty pumped about this vision and plan to spend the next several years developing it in one form or another.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
